A Guide to the Papers of the Dean of Students, ca. 1968-1970, 1980-2005
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Dean of Students ca. 1968-1970, 1980-2005
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/2/1.052
ca. 12,000 items (40 Hollinger boxes, ca. 17 linear feet)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions apply to personally identifiable student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the Special Collections Archives from the Office of the Dean of Students, Peabody Hall, University of Virginia, through Rhonda F. Saunders on February 3, 2005.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the papers from the Office of the Vice President for Student Affairs (formerly Dean of Students), ca. 12,000 items (40 Hollinger boxes, ca. 17 linear feet), ca. 1968-1970 and 1980- 2005, the administrative files of Dean of Students Robert T. Canevari, Associate and Assistant Deans of Students Ronald J. Stump and Michele Samuels, Senior Associate Dean of Students and Director of Student Life Shamim Sisson, Assistant Dean for Latino/Hispanic Students Pablo J. Davis, Assistant Deans for Asian Pacific America Programs Glenna C. Chang, Ajay T. Nair, and Daisy P. Rodriguez.
The papers include reports, correspondence, memoranda, budgets, manuals, surveys, membership lists, events calendars, handouts, sample packets for students, and some printed material.
The collection also contains eight computer diskettes (Disks 0322--0322-g) labeled with catch words such as "Family weekend," "Peer Advising and Family Network," "T-shirt," "APA," "PAFN Brochure" and "Hispanic Student Survey 1994."
Arrangement
These papers came from the Dean of Students Office grouped into eight series and these series were maintained:
Series I: Files of Robert T. Canevari, Dean of Students (Boxes 1-10)
Series II: Files of Ronald J. Stump and Michele Samuels, Associate and Assistant Dean of Students (Boxes 10-14)
Series III: Files of Shamim Sisson, Senior Associate Dean of Students and Director of Student Life (Boxes 14-20)
Series IV: Files of Pablo J. Davis, Assistant Dean for Latino/Hispanic Students (Boxes 20-22)
Series V: Files of Glenna C. Chang, Assistant Dean for Asian Pacific American Programs (Boxes 22-29)
Series VI: Files of Ajay T. Nair, Assistant Dean of Students for Asian Pacific American Students (Boxes 29-32)
Series VII: Files of Ajay T. Nair and Daisy P. Rodriguez, Assistant Dean for Asian Pacific American Students (Boxes 32-35)
Series VIII: Restricted Files (Boxes 36-40)
Contents List
- Series I: Files of Robert T. Canevari, Dean of Students
  - (Vice President) Advisory Committee on Alcohol and Substance Abuse 1998-1999 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - Alcohol Awareness/Miscellaneous 1997-1999 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - Alcohol Awareness/Miscellaneous 1996 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - Alcohol Education and Prevention Programs Committee 1998-2000 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Alcohol Policy 1987-1999 (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Alumni Association 1996-1999 (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Alumni Association--Reunions 1997-2000 (Box-folder 1:7)
  - Americans for Disability Act Programs 1995 (Box-folder 1:8)
  - Black Fraternal Council 1993-2000 (Box-folder 1:9)
  - Black Student Life--Miscellaneous 1968, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 1:10)
  - Board of Visitors 1999 May-2000 Jun (Box-folder 2:1)
  - Board of Visitors 1998 Jul-1999 Jun (Box-folder 2:2)
  - Board of Visitors--Report to BOV on Fraternity Rush 1999 (Box-folder 2:3)
  - Board of Visitors--Report to BOV on Fraternity Rush 1998 (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Budgets: Office of Dean of Students, Residence Life Office 1998-1999 (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Budget: Vice President for Management 1993-1998 (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Business Operations 1990-1992 (Box-folder 2:7)
  - Calendar--Major Events 1991-1992 (Box-folder 2:8)
  - The Cavalier Daily 1997-1998 (Box-folder 2:9)
  - Class Councils--First Year Council 1997-1998 (Box-folder 2:10)
  - Class Councils--Graduating Class/Trustees 1999 1997-1999 (Box-folder 2:11)
  - Class Councils--Graduating Class/Trustees 2000 1999-2000 (Box-folder 2:12)
  - Class Councils--Second Year Council 1999-2000 1999 (Box-folder 3:1)
  - Class Councils--Second Year Council 1998-1999 1998-1999 (Box-folder 3:2)
  - Class Councils--Third Year Council 1999-2000 1999 (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Class Councils--Third Year Council 1998-1999 1998-1999 (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Corks & Curls 1986-1998 (Box-folder 3:5)
  - Cultural Programming Board 1999 (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Dining Services 1994-1996 (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Education, School of 1989-1998 (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Emergencies 1969-1994 (Box-folder 3:9)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action 1990-1999 (Box-folder 3:10)
  - Faculty Reimbursement 1994-1999 (Box-folder 3:11)
  - Family Weekend 1997-1999 (Box-folder 3:12)
  - First Year Enrollment 1998-1999 (Box-folder 3:13)
  - First Year Faces Book 1983-2000 (Box-folder 3:14)
  - Fraternities 1997-1999 (Box-folder 3:15)
  - Fraternity Alumni Council 1998 (Box-folder 3:16)
  - Fraternity Rush Proposal 1998 May-Sep (Box-folder 3:17)
  - Fraternity Rush Proposal 1998 Apr (Box-folder 3:18)
  - Fraternity Rush Proposal 1998 Mar 19-31 (Box-folder 4:1)
  - Fraternity Rush Proposal 1998 Mar 1-18 (Box-folder 4:2)
  - Fraternity Rush Proposal 1996-1998 Jan (Box-folder 4:3)
  - Freedom of Speech 1989-1995 (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Fundraising for Student Organizations 1996-1998 (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Historic Renovation Corporation 1999 (Box-folder 4:6)
  - Honor Committee 1998-1999 (Box-folder 4:7)
  - Housing--Language Houses 1996-1998 (Box-folder 4:8)
  - Housing--Mosaic House 1995-1998 (Box-folder 4:9)
  - Information Technology and Communication 1993-1999 (Box-folder 5:1)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5:2)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council--Rush 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5:3)
  - Inter-Sorority Council 1998-2000 (Box-folder 5:4)
  - International Center Advisory 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5:5)
  - Intramural Department 1992-1998 (Box-folder 5:6)
  - Judiciary Committee 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5:7)
  - Judiciary Committee--Athletic Event Misconduct Procedures 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5:8)
  - Law School 1988-1995 (Box-folder 5:9)
  - Lawn Organizing Committee 1997-1998 (Box-folder 5:10)
  - Leadership--UVA Lead 1999-2000 (Box-folder 5:11)
  - Leadership--Leadership 2000 1998 (Box-folder 5:12)
  - Longitudinal Study of Undergraduate Education--Class of 1999 Interim Report: Results from the Third-Year Survey 1999 (Box-folder 5:13)
  - Medical Center (Medical/Nursing School) 1996-1997 (Box-folder 5:14)
  - Minority Concerns/Focus 1995-1996 (Box-folder 5:15)
  - Office of Dean of Students--Benchmarking Project 1998 Jun-1999 (Box-folder 5:16)
  - Office of Dean of Students--Benchmarking Project 1994-1998 May (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Office of Dean of Students--Cultural Support Team 1997-1999 (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Office of Dean of Students--Office Retreat--January 1999 1998-1999 (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Office of Dean of Students--Position on Discrimination 1998 (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Office of Dean of Students--Staff Meetings 1999 (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Office of Dean of Students--Staff Meetings 1998 (Box-folder 6:6)
  - Office of Dean of Students--Staff Memos 1993-1998 (Box-folder 6:7)
  - Office of Dean of Students--Transfer Program 1999-2000 (Box-folder 6:8)
  - Office of Senior Vice President and Chief Financial Officer 1994-1999 (Box-folder 6:9)
  - Orientation--Grounds for Discussion 1997-1998 (Box-folder 6:10)
  - Orientation--Letter to Parents of First Year Students 1995-1999 (Box-folder 6:11)
  - Orientation Planning 1998 (Box-folder 6:12)
  - Orientation--Summer Orientation 1999 (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Orientation--Summer Orientation--Student Life Issues Team/Joining the University of Virginia Community Team 1998-1999 (Box-folder 7:2)
  - Orientation--University of Virginia 2002 1998 (Box-folder 7:3)
  - Parents Funding 1998-1999 (Box-folder 7:4)
  - Parking/Transportation, Department of 1994-1999 (Box-folder 7:5)
  - Peabody Hall Renovation 1999 (Box-folder 7:6)
  - President's Retreat 1998 (Box-folder 7:7)
  - Processions Subcommittee--Commencement and Convocation Committee 1996-1998 (Box-folder 7:8)
  - Programming Board 1977-78, 1998-99 (Box-folder 7:9)
  - Racial Harassment/Homophobic 1988-1997 (Box-folder 7:10)
  - Residence Life--Brown College on Monroe Hill 1996-1998 (Box-folder 7:11)
  - Residence Life--Coffee House/Tuttle 1998 (Box-folder 7:12)
  - Residence Life--First Year Student Residential Initiatives 1998-1999 (Box-folder 7:13)
  - Residence Life--Hereford College (New College) 1995-1998 (Box-folder 7:14)
  - Residences Life--International Residential College 1999 (Box-folder 7:15)
  - Residence Life--Munford/Gwathmey Residential College 1997 (Box-folder 7:16)
  - Residence Life Office 1998-1999 (Box-folder 7:17)
  - Resident Staff 1998-2000 (Box-folder 7:18)
  - Residential House Councils 1994-1999 (Box-folder 8:1)
  - Seven Society/Secret Societies 1982-1997 (Box-folder 8:2)
  - Solicitation 1994-1999 (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Sororities, including "The Sorority Report" and a class paper "History of Sororities at the University of Virginia" 1980, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 8:4)
  - Spring Fling 1997 (Box-folder 8:5)
  - Student Affairs, Vice President for 1997-2001 (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Student Activities Committee, Annual Report to the 1998-1999 (Box-folder 8:7)
  - Student Council 1998 (Box-folder 8:8)
  - Student Council--Escort Van 1994-1996 (Box-folder 8:9)
  - Student Health, Department of 1994-1998 (Box-folder 8:10)
  - Student Organizations--Miscellaneous 1996-1999 (Box-folder 8:11)
  - Symbols--Painting of, on University Property/Buildings 1983-89, 1995-97 (Box-folder 8:12)
  - "University of Virginia Celebrates 250 Years of Thomas Jefferson's Pursuit of Knowledge"--Interviews with Four Presidents, Edgar F. Shannon, Jr., Frank L. Hereford, Jr., Robert M. O'Neil and John T. Casteen, III 1993 (Box-folder 9:1)
  - University of Virginia Police Department 1997-2000 (Box-folder 9:2)
  - University Relations 1994-1998 (Box-folder 9:3)
  - University Retreat 1999 (Box-folder 9:4)
  - University Union 1999 (Box-folder 9:5)
  - University Union Concerts 1989-1998 (Box-folder 9:6)
  - University Union and Student Activities Building, Committee on 1999 Sep-2000 (Box-folder 9:7)
  - University Union and Student Activities Building, Committee on 1999 Jan-May (Box-folder 9:8)
  - University Union and Student Activities Building, Committee on 1998 (Box-folder 9:9)
  - University Union Report 1999-2000 (Box-folder 10:1)
  - UVA Cares 1998 (Box-folder 10:2)
  - Warning Given by Robert T. Canevari concerning Trespassing on University Property Warning Given by Robert T. Canevari concerning Trespassing on University Property (Box-folder 10:3)
  - WTJU Radio Station 1997 (Box-folder 10:4)
- Series II: Files of Ronald J. Stump and Michele Samuels, Associate and Assistant Dean of Students
  - Board of Visitors Student Activity Fee Guidelines 1989-1995 (Box-folder 10:5)
  - "Empowering the Leaders of Tomorrow" 1998 (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Fall Appropriations 1995 (Box-folder 10:7)
  - First Year Focus Program 1996 (Box-folder 10:8)
  - Grounds for Discussion 1999, 2000 (Box-folder 10:9)
  - Grounds for Discussion 1997-1998 (Box-folder 10:10)
  - Grounds for Discussion (Binder Contents) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 10:11)
  - Grounds for Discussion--Binder Contents 1997-1998 (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Grounds for Discussion--Casts, Scripts, Publicity, Miscellaneous 1996-1998 (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Grounds for Discussion--Evaluations/Results 1996 (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Grounds for Discussion--Facilitating 1998, 1999 (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Grounds for Discussion--Planning 1998, 1999 (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Historical Listings of Contracted Independent Organizations 1993 Sep-1996 (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Historical Listings of Contracted Independent Organizations 1988-1993 May (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Kaleidoscope 1998-2000 (Box-folder 12:1)
  - Serve - Community Service Projects (Binder Contents) 2000 (Box-folder 12:2)
  - Serve - Community Service Projects (Binder Contents) 1999 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Serve - Community Service Projects (Binder Contents) 1998 (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Serve - Community Service Projects (Binder Contents) 1997 (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Serve - Community Service Projects (Binder Contents) 1996 (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Serve - Community Service Projects (Binder Contents) 1995 (Box-folder 12:7)
  - Student Activities Committee 1995 May-Jul (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1995 Jan-Apr (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Student Activities Committee 1994 Nov-Dec (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Student Activities Committee 1993-1994 Oct (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Student Activities Committee--Meeting Minutes 1987-1998 (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Student Activity Fee--Appropriations Roles 1993-1995 (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Student Activity Fee--Funding Guidelines Revisions 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13:7)
  - Student Activity Fee--Purpose Statement and Guidelines 1987-1995 (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Tipton v. University of Hawaii 1993-1994 (Box-folder 14:2)
- Series III: Files of Shamim Sisson, Senior Associate Dean of Students and Director of Student Life
  - Contacts, Students 2002-2003 (Box-folder 14:3)
  - Dean of Students--New Colleague Welcome Orientation Packet 2000-2001 (Box-folder 14:4)
  - Dean of Students--On-Call Manual 2000-2001 (Box-folder 14:5)
  - Dean of Students--Peabody Deans 1997-2001 (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Dean of Students--Student Life Deans 2001-2002 (Box-folder 14:7)
  - Family Weekend 1997-1999 (Box-folder 14:8)
  - Family Weekend--Evaluations by School 1996 (Box-folder 14:9)
  - Family Weekend--Photographs 1990, n.d. (Box-folder 14:10)
  - First Year Seminar 2001-2002 (Box-folder 15:1)
  - First Year Seminar 2000-2001 (Box-folder 15:2)
  - First Year Seminar--Evaluations/Summary 2001-2002 (Box-folder 15:3)
  - First Year Seminar--Exit Interviews 2001-2002 (Box-folder 15:4)
  - First Year Seminar--Facilitator Exit Interviews 2000-2001 (Box-folder 15:5)
  - First Year Seminar--Miscellaneous 1998-2003 (Box-folder 15:6)
  - First Year Seminar Packet 2000 (Box-folder 15:7)
  - First Year Seminar Packet 2001 (Box-folder 15:8)
  - First Year Seminar Packet 2002 (Box-folder 15:9)
  - First Year Seminar Packet 2003 (Box-folder 15:10)
  - First Year Seminar--Photos 1981-1982 (Box-folder 15:11)
  - Leadership 2003 2002-2003 (Box-folder 16:1)
  - Leadership 2003--Manual 2003 (Box-folder 16:2)
  - Leadership 2002 2001-2002 (Box-folder 16:3)
  - Leadership 2002--Assessment Projects A and B 2002 (Box-folder 16:4)
  - Leadership 2002--Manual 2002 (Box-folder 16:5)
  - Leadership 2002--Reservations/Financial 2002 (Box-folder 16:6)
  - Leadership 2001 2000-2001 (Box-folder 16:7)
  - Leadership 2001--Manual 2001 (Box-folder 17:1)
  - Leadership 2001--Reservations/Financial 2001 (Box-folder 17:2)
  - Leadership 2000 1999-2000 (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Leadership 2000--Reservations/Financial 2000 (Box-folder 17:4)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bi-Sexual, Transgender Resource Center n.d. (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bi-Sexual, Transgender Resource Center n.d. (Box-folder 17:6)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bi-Sexual, Transgender Resource Center 2002 (Box-folder 17:7)
  - Mediation 1997-2002 (Box-folder 18:1)
  - Melissa D. Holland Award 2003 (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Melissa D. Holland Award 1983-2002 (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Orientation 2000-2003 (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Phi Eta Sigma 2000-2002 (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Phi Eta Sigma 2000-2003 (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Phi Eta Sigma--Local Scholarships 1997-2002 (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Phi Eta Sigma--Membership Lists 1995-2001 (Box-folder 18:8)
  - Phi Eta Sigma--National Scholarship 1999-2003 (Box-folder 18:9)
  - Phi Eta Sigma--Publication Forum 2000-2003 (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Sean Bryant Award 2003 2002-2003 (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Sean Bryant Scholarship 1997-2002 (Box-folder 19:3)
  - Sexual Assault Board 2002 (Box-folder 19:4)
  - Sexual Assault Board 1998-2001 (Box-folder 19:5)
  - Sexual Assault Board 1999-2000 (Box-folder 19:6)
  - Strategic Planning--Comprehensive Leadership Program Subcommittee 2001 May (Box-folder 19:7)
  - Strategic Planning--Comprehensive Leadership Program Subcommittee 2000-2001 Apr (Box-folder 19:8)
  - Student Contacts 1999-2001 (Box-folder 19:9)
  - Students with Children 2002 Aug-2003 (Box-folder 19:10)
  - Students with Children 1999-2002 May (Box-folder 19:11)
  - Students with Children--Advisory Board 2002-2003 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Transportation and Parking 2001-2002 (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Undergrad Student Parents' Outreach 1999-2000 (Box-folder 20:3)
  - Women's Leadership and Development Program--Manual 2003 2003 (Box-folder 20:4)
  - Women's Leadership and Development Program--Manual 2001 2000-2001 (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Women's Leadership and Development Program--Manual 2000 1999-2000 (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Women's Leadership and Development Program--Manual 1999 1998-1999 (Box-folder 20:7)
  - Women's Leadership and Development Program--Resource Lists 2000-2001 (Box-folder 20:7)
- Series IV: Files of Pablo J. Davis, Assistant Dean for Latino/Hispanic Students
  - Alianza 2000 (Box-folder 20:8)
  - Bolivar Network 1999-2000 (Box-folder 20:9)
  - Bolivar Network/Hispanic Alumni 1997 (Box-folder 20:10)
  - Delta Upsilon Banner/Bridge Slurs 2000-2001 (Box-folder 20:11)
  - El Calendario 2002-2003 (Box-folder 21:1)
  - El Calendario 1999-2001 (Box-folder 21:2)
  - El Calendario --Administrative 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21:3)
  - Family Weekend 1999 (Box-folder 21:4)
  - Hispanic/Latino Executive Summary 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21:5)
  - Hispanic/Latino Faculty Graduation Reception 1999 (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Hispanic/Latino Issues 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21:7)
  - Hispanic/Latino Organizations at University of Virginia 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21:8)
  - Hispanic/Latino Outreach Budget 1998-2000 (Box-folder 21:9)
  - Hispanic/Latino Student Leadership Conference 1997-1998 (Box-folder 21:10)
  - Hispanic/Latino Student Lists 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21:11)
  - Hispanic/Latino Welcome Reception 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21:12)
  - Hispanic Awareness Week 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21:13)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month 1999 (Box-folder 21:14)
  - Hispanic Leadership Seminar 1995-1996 (Box-folder 21:15)
  - Hispanic Outlook 2000 (Box-folder 21:16)
  - Hispanic Recruitment 1994 (Box-folder 21:17)
  - Hispanic Students Roundtable 1988-1989 (Box-folder 21:18)
  - Hispanic Students Survey 1994-1996 (Box-folder 21:19)
  - India Day Welcome Remarks n.d. (Box-folder 21:20)
  - La Rueda 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21:21)
  - La Sociedad Latina 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21:22)
  - La Voz 1998 (Box-folder 22:1)
  - Latino Round Table 2000 (Box-folder 22:2)
  - Latino Student Admissions Committee/Latino Recruitment 1999-2000 (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Leadership Conference--Hispanic/Latino 1996 (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Leadership Seminar--Hispanic/Latino 1996-1997 (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Leadership Seminar--Hispanic/Native American 1994-1995 (Box-folder 22:6)
  - "Nuestra America/Our America" 1999 (Box-folder 22:7)
  - Peer Mentor Programs 1998-2001 (Box-folder 22:8)
  - Peer Mentor Programs--Training Day, Scripts and Scenarios 1999-2000 (Box-folder 22:9)
  - Red de Apoyo/Support Network/Letter and List 1999-2000 (Box-folder 22:10)
  - Salvador Earthquake 2001 (Box-folder 22:11)
- Series V: Files of Glenna C. Chang, Assistant Dean for Asian Pacific American Programs
  - Alumni Issues 1996-2000 Jan (Box-folder 22:12)
  - Alumni Issues 2000 Feb-Jun (Box-folder 22:13)
  - Alumni Survey--Asian Pacific American 1998 (Box-folder 22:14)
  - Asian American Cultural Center Career Connections 1996 (Box-folder 22:15)
  - Asian American Internet Guide 1995 (Box-folder 22:16)
  - Asian American Leadership Seminar 1996-1997 (Box-folder 22:17)
  - 15% Asian American Students (Faculty/Administrators Meeting) 2000-2001 (Box-folder 23:1)
  - Asian American Student Conference 1995-1998 (Box-folder 23:2)
  - Asian American Student Conference 1997-1998 (Box-folder 23:3)
  - Asian American Student Conference--Welcome Remarks 1995 (Box-folder 23:4)
  - Asian and Asian Pacific American Alumni Network 1998-2001 (Box-folder 23:5)
  - Asian Leadership Council 1998-2001 (Box-folder 23:6)
  - Asian Leadership Council--Calendar 1998-1999 (Box-folder 23:7)
  - Asian Pacific American Faculty and Staff 1998-1999 (Box-folder 23:8)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--General 1998-1999 (Box-folder 23:9)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Fall 1999 1999 (Box-folder 23:10)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Fall 1999--Applications 1999 (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Fall 1999 Nominees 1999 (Box-folder 24:2)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Handouts 1999 (Box-folder 24:3)
  - Asian Pacific American Leadership Training Institute--Spring 1999 1998-1999 (Box-folder 24:4)
  - Asian Pacific American--Miscellaneous 1998-1999 (Box-folder 24:5)
  - Asian Pacific American Organizations Contact Information 2000 (Box-folder 24:6)
  - Asian Pacific American Resource Guide 1998 (Box-folder 24:7)
  - Asian Pacific American Student Leaders Handbook 2002-2003 (Box-folder 24:8)
  - Asian Pacific American Survey 1993-1998 (Box-folder 24:9)
  - Asian Student Council n.d. (Box-folder 24:10)
  - Asian Student Union 1999 Oct-2001 (Box-folder 24:11)
  - Asian Student Union 1998-1999 Sep (Box-folder 25:1)
  - Asian Student Union--Five Year Plan 1994 (Box-folder 25:2)
  - Asian Student Union--Leadership Training 1998 (Box-folder 25:3)
  - Asian Student Union--Money 2000 (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Beyond Black and White Resource Guide 2001 (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Brown Bag Lunch Series 1999 (Box-folder 25:6)
  - Brown Bag Lunch Series--Asian Pacific American 1999 (Box-folder 25:7)
  - [Contracted Independent Organizations] Lambda Theta Alpha Latin Sorority, Inc. n.d. (Box-folder 25:8)
  - Coalition 2002 (Box-folder 25:9)
  - Educational/Cultural Programming Request for Financial Support 2001 (Box-folder 25:10)
  - Gender--Asian Pacific American Female 1998-1999 (Box-folder 25:11)
  - Gender--Asian Pacific American Male 1999 (Box-folder 25:12)
  - Gender--Young Asian Women's Alliance 1999 (Box-folder 25:13)
  - Grounds for Discussion 2001 (Box-folder 25:14)
  - Grounds for Discussion--Flyers and Clip Art 2000-2001 (Box-folder 25:15)
  - Honor 2001 (Box-folder 25:16)
  - Identity Development 2001 (Box-folder 25:17)
  - Janis and Ray Meetings 2000 (Box-folder 25:18)
  - Kaleidoscope 1999-2000 (Box-folder 26:1)
  - Kaleidoscope 2000-2001 (Box-folder 26:2)
  - Kaleidoscope--Admission 2001 (Box-folder 26:3)
  - Kaleidoscope--History--Multiethnic/Interracial Forum 1997-1999 (Box-folder 26:4)
  - Kaleidoscope-- Interrace Back Issues 1994-2000 (Box-folder 26:5)
  - Kaleidoscope--Mailing List 2001 (Box-folder 26:6)
  - Lambda Phi Epsilon 1999-2002 (Box-folder 26:7)
  - Longitudinal Study of Undergraduate Education--Results from the Fourth-Year Survey 2000 (Box-folder 26:8)
  - Mentorship Program with APAMSA (Asian Pacific American Medical Student Association) 1998 (Box-folder 26:9)
  - Nelson S. Chow Award 1997 (Box-folder 26:10)
  - News Clips 1998-2003 (Box-folder 26:11)
  - Organization of Young Filipino Americans--Class Development 1996-1997 (Box-folder 26:12)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network 1999 (Box-folder 26:13)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Advisors 1999 (Box-folder 26:14)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Catering 1999 (Box-folder 26:15)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Committees 2000-2001 (Box-folder 26:16)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Evaluations 1999 (Box-folder 26:17)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Faculty Information Sheets 1999 (Box-folder 27:1)
  - Peer Advising and Family Network--Family Network Members 1999-2000 (Box-folder 27:2)